Subhankar Banik

Subhankar

Experienced with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in C++, C, HTML5, CSS3, Communication, Digital Marketing, Google AdMob and Video Editing. Strong community and social services professional with a Bachelor of Technology focused in Production Engineering from National Institute of Technology Agartala.

- ≥ subhankarbanik23@gmail.com
- Agartala, Tripura, India
- S https://join.skype.com/invite/iivWQ6EvVe0a

8837496744

- in linkedin.com/in/subhankar-banik-2643401b3
- github.com/Subhankar-23

EDUCATION

Production Engineering

National Institute of Technology Agartala

07/2019 - Present

Higher Senior Secondary

Swami Dhananjay Das Kathia Baba Mission School

2017 - 2019 Agartala

Senior Secondary

Sri Krishna Mission School

2005 - 2017 Agartala

WORK EXPERIENCE

Coordinator of Volunteers

Script Production

02/2020 - 07/2020

Contact: https://scriptproductionsofficial.wordpress.com/

Internshala Student Partner 19 Internshala

08/2020 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

Student Partner

Community Leader Unschool

08/2020 - Present

E-learning platform of India

Achievements/Tasks

Community Leader of UNSCHOOL

Contact: http://www.unschool.in/

Publisher Engagement Intern POKKT

11/2020 - 05/2021

POKKT is a leading mobile video advertising platform in India, South East Asia & MENA with a strong focus on rewarded Video Ads within Mobile Games. POKKT is integrated with over 300 Top Games and App Developers in India, MENA and South East Asia. By Integrating POKKT SDK, Developers in the region can monetize their non-paying users and maximize eCPMs through highly-targeted brand video Ads within their Apps.

Achievements/Tasks

Publisher Engagement

Contact: Arjun Chadha - https://www.linkedin.com/in/arjunchadha

SKILLS



CERTIFICATES

C Language (05/2020 - Present)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/18E9TUUg6JWQdZ4kw5xnVB3Ze9GIXnE Ys/view?usp=sharing

HTML5 (06/2020 - Present)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1550-CeYl3NgMGW8ML3TkH95uTFyFiGPq/view?usp=sharing

Advanced Java (05/2020 - Present)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/15CNMk3iGKk8tsQ5p37xBVrcbVE63Gqf 2/view?usp=sharing

Digital Marketing (07/2020 - Present)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1TpRRmXohtyxMtCTi-roiJmebeQwWl8tj/view?usp=sharing

Video Editing (09/2020 - Present)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/16cQpXxvc6IUKqvDj6yMREWXXd4NHXE bF/view?usp=sharing

Workshop on ML & IoT (03/2020 - Present)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/18LXTTVEgsbjJUx6z13EFp_NSknCPORu o/view?usp=sharing

Event Management & Marketing Intern (07/2020 - Present)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/15WFad5Aki-BNE4Re6sb4dWtVRYRD5Jgy/view?usp=sharing

E-quiz on Microprocessor (07/2020 - Present)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/119QGFEPDjj9Tb1dxi_okkYVPeXLRKROZ /view?usp=sharing

LANGUAGES

English Hi

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

Video Editing

Bengali

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Web Development

Digital Marketing